http://www.alaskanational.com/policyholder/claim-forms

PacificComp
Need Help?
Agent/Broker Login
CopperPoint
Alaska National
PacificComp
Need Help?
En Español
You are about to leave the website of CopperPoint Insurance Companies and view the content of an external website.
Claims Kit
When it comes to the complexities of workers’ compensation, you can rely on our deep expertise to help you navigate specific state regulations and claims forms. These resources provide the valuable information and tools you need when dealing with a workplace injury.
For help identifying your insurance company, please contact us at 800.231.1363.
Insurance Company*
- Select One -
CopperPoint
Alaska National
PacificComp
Resource*
- Select One -
Claims Kit
Reset
Your Claims Kit will include:
State Forms
Posters & Brochures
State Compliance Information
Injured Worker Resources
Documents Provided by CopperPoint, Alaska National and PacificComp
Arizona
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Colorado
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
New Mexico
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Utah
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Nevada
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Alabama
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Alaska
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Arkansas
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
California
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Connenticut
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Delaware
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Florida
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Georgia
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Hawaii
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Idaho
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Illinois
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Indiana
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Iowa
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Kansas
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Kentucky
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Louisiana
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Maine
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Massachusetts
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Maryland
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Michigan
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Minnesota
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Mississippi
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Missouri
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Montana
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Nebraska
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
New Hampshire
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
New Jersey
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
New York
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
North Carolina
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
North Dakota
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Ohio
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Oklahoma
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Oregon
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Rhode Island
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Pennslyvania
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
South Carolina
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
South Dakota
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Tenneessee
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Texas
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Vermont
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Virginia
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Washington
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
West Virginia
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Wisconsin
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Wyoming
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByCopperPoint Insurance Company3030 North 3rd StreetPhoenix, AZ 85012
Email: ask@copperpoint.comPhone: 602.631.2300Phone: 800.231.1363
Alabama
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208.955.8036Fax: 208.780.7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Arizona
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208.955.8036Fax: 208.780.7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Arkansas
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208.955.8036Fax: 208.780.7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Alaska
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208.955.8036Fax: 208.780.7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
California
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208.955.8036Fax: 208.780.7943sfo_claims@alaskanational.com
Colorado
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208.955.8036Fax: 208.780.7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Connecticut
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208.955.8036Fax: 208.780.7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Delaware
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208.955.8036Fax: 208.780.7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Florida
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Georgia
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Hawaii
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Idaho
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Illinois
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Indiana
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Iowa
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Kansas
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Kentucky
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Louisiana
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Maine
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Massachusetts
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Maryland
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Michigan
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Minnesota
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Mississippi
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Missouri
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Montana
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Nebraska
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Nevada
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
New Hampshire
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
New Jeresy
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
New Mexico
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
New York
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
North Carolina
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
North Dakota
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Ohio
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Oklahoma
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Oregon
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Pennslyvania
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Rhode Island
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
South Carolina
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
South Dakota
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Tennessee
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Texas
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Utah
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Vermont
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Virginia
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Washington
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
West Virginia
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Wisconsin
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
Wyoming
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled By
Alaska National Insurance Company2501 E State Ave., Suite 100Meridian, ID 83642208-955-8036Fax: (208) 780-7943boi_claims@alaskanational.com
California
Claims Kit Contents
Claims Handled ByPacificComp Insurance CompanyP.O. Box 5042Thousand Oaks, CA 91359-5042
Forms
Agreement Between Employer / Employee Choice of Physician
Agreement Between Employer / Employee Choice of Physician (Spanish)
Alternative Choice of Physician or Chiropractor
Application for 104 Weeks Dependents' Benefits
Application for Fatal Dependents' Benefits
Authorization and Request for Unemployment
Average Weekly Wage Certification
Average Weekly Wage Certification-Concurrent
Average Weekly Wage Certification-Post Injury
Average Weekly Wage Computation Schedule
Average Weekly Wage Worksheet
Choice of Doctor
Choice of Doctor (Spanish)
Claimant's First Notice of Death and Claim for Compensation
Employee Report of Occupational Injury or Illness to Employer
Employee's Claim for Compensation / Report of Initial Treatment
Employee's First Notice of Accidental Injury and Claim for Compensation.
Employee's First Notice of Occupational Disease and Claim for Compensation
Employee's Notice of Rejection of Terms of the Arizona
Workers' Compensation Law
Employee's Notice of Rejection of Terms of the Arizona
Workers' Compensation Law
Employee's Wage Report
Employees Claim and Employer First Report of Injury
Employees Notice of Injury and Claim for Compensation
Employees' and Physicians' Report of Occupational Hearing Loss
Employees' and Physicians' Report of Occupational Injury or Disease
Employees' Report of Occupational Pneumoconiosis
Employer First Report of Injury / Fatality
Employer First Report of Injury or Disease
Employer Report of Employee Earnings - formerly Wage Statement (C-94A)
Employer Report of Employee Earnings - formerly Wage Statement (C-94A) (Spanish)
Employer Report of Occupational Injury or Illness to Division of Workers' Compensation
Employer's First Report of Alleged Occupational Injury or Disease
Employer's First Report of Injury
Employer's First Report of Injury
Employer's First Report of Injury
Employer's First Report of Injury
Must be submitted electronically.
Employer's First Report of Injury or Illness
Employer's First Report of Injury or Illness
Employer's First Report of Injury or Occupational Disease
Employer's First Report of Injury or Occupational Disease.
Employer's First Report of Occupational Injury or Disease
Employer's First Report of Occupational Injury or Disease
Employer's First Report of Occupational Injury or Disease Form
Employer's First Report of Occupational Injury or Illness
Employer's Modified Duty Availability Report
Employer's Modified Duty Availability Report
Employer's Multiple Employment Wage Statement
Employer's Multiple Employment Wage Statement (Spanish)
Employer's Report for Reimbursement of Voluntary Payment
Employer's Report for Reimbursement of Voluntary Payment
Employer's Report of Employee's Injury or Occupational Disease to the Industrial Commission
Employer's Report of Industrial Injury
Employer's Report of Industrial Injury or Occupational Disease
Employer's Report of Injury
Employer's Report of Non-covered Employee's Occupational Injury or Disease
Employer's Report of Occupational Injury or Illness
Required
Employer's Report of Work-Related Injury/Illness
Employer's Report of Work-Related Injury/Illness (Spanish)
Employer's Statement of Wage Earnings
(C-240) (Preceding The Date of Injury/Illness)
Employer's Supplemental Report
Employer's Supplemental Report of Injury
Employer's Wage Statement
Employer's Wage Statement (Spanish)
Employer's Wage Statement for School Districts
Employer's Wage Statement for School Districts (Spanish)
Employer's Wage Verification Form
Employers First Report of Injury or Illness
Employers Report of Accident
Employers' First Notice of Injury
Employers' Report of Occupational Injury or Disease
Fatality Report
Required
First Report of Alleged Occupational Injury or Illness
First Report of an Injury, Occupational Disease or Death
First Report of an Injury, Occupational Disease or Death (Spanish)
First Report of Injury
First Report of Injury
First Report of Injury
First Report of Injury
First Report of Injury
First Report of Injury
First Report of Injury
First Report of Injury (FR01)
First Report of Injury (FROI)
First Report of Injury - Employer's form
First Report of Injury and Occupational Disease (FROI)
First Report of Injury Instructions
First Report of Injury or Illness
First Report of Injury or Illness
First Report of Injury or Illness
First Report of Injury or Illness
First Report of Injury or Illness
First Report of Injury or Illness
First Report of Injury or Illness
First Report of Occupational Fatality
Missouri Census of Fatal Occupational Injuries
First Report of Occupational Injury or Disease
First Report of Work Injury ( C-20 )
Fraud & Compliance Unit Claim Referral/Initial Information Report
Required
General Admission of Liability
Glossary of Workers' Compensation Terms for Injured Workers
Governmental Entities Agreement Between Employer / Employee Choice of Physician Form
Initial Statement of Insurance Carrier / Self Insurer with Respect to Payment of Benefits
Injured Workers' Rights and Responsibilities
Insurance Company Fraud Contact Form
Medical Treatment for Your Work Injury or Occupational Illness
Medical Waiver and Consent
Mileage Reimbursement Form
Notice of Accident or Occupational Disease Disablement (English and Spanish)
Notice of Accident to Employer and Claim of Employee, Representative, or Dependent
Notice of Accident to Employer and Claim of Employee, Representative, or Dependent (Spanish)
Notice of Accidental Injury or Occupational Disease
Notice of Designated Physician
Notice of Employee Death
Required
Notice of Injury or Occupational Disease (Incident Report)
Notice of Personal Chiropractor or Personal Acupuncturist
Notice of Personal Chiropractor or Personal Acupuncturist (Spanish)
OCR-Employer's Basic Report of Injury
Plaintiff's Chronological Medical History
Predesignation of Personal Physician
Predesignation of Personal Physician (Spanish)
Program Review Report
Report of Fatal Accident
Report of Injury
Report of Injury or Illness
Required
Report of Injury or Illness (Spanish)
Required
Request for a Rotating Rating Physician or Chiropractor
Request for Extension of Time
Request for Social Security Disability Benefit Information
Schedule of Dependent(s) and Filing Status Statement
Schedule of Dependent(s) and Filing Status Statement
Schedule of Dependent(s) and Filing Status Statement
Statement of Days Worked and Earnings of Injured Employee
Statement of Earnings of Injured Employee
Statement of Wage Information
Statement of Wages
Statement of Weekly Earnings
Subsequent Report
Subsequent Report of Injury (SROI)
Supplemental Report
Supplemental Report of Fatal Injury
Supplemental Report of Injury
Required
Supplemental Report of Return to Work
Suspected Insurance Fraud Citizen Reporting Form
Uniform Suspected Insurance Fraud Reporting
Wage Calculation Form for Claims Agent's Use
Workers' Compensation - First Report of Injury or Illness
Workers' Compensation Claim form (Employee)
Required
Workers' Compensation Claim form (Employee) - Bilingual
Required
Posters and Brochures
NOTICE - Important Information for Injured Employees -
(Spanish)
Required
OFFICIAL NOTICE Panel of Physicians
Required
"A Guide for Workers" Recently Hurt on the Job"
Required
"A Guide for Workers" Recently Hurt on the Job"(Spanish)
Required
Posters are only required for certain agricultural operations. If you are agricultural check "Posting Requirements" under the "Compliance Information".
A Beginners Guide to Tennessee Workers Compensation Claims (Spanish)
A Guide to Workers" Compensation in Wyoming
Already Have a Poster? Fill out this Label
Answers to Your Questions about Permanent Disability Benefits
Answers to Your Questions about Permanent Disability Benefits (Spanish)
Answers to Your Questions about Qualified Medical Evaluators and Agreed Medical Evaluators
Answers to Your Questions about Qualified Medical Evaluators and Agreed Medical Evaluators (Spanish)
Answers to Your Questions about Temporary Disability Benefits
Answers to Your Questions about Temporary Disability Benefits (Spanish)
Answers to Your Questions about the State's Uninsured Employers Benefits Trust Fund
Answers to Your Questions about the State's Uninsured Employers Benefits Trust Fund (Spanish)
Answers to Your Questions about Utilization Review
Answers to Your Questions about Utilization Review (Spanish)
BROCHURE -
Workers" Compensation Information for Kansas Employers and Employees (Spanish)
BROCHURE -
Injured Workers
BROCHURE -
Injured Workers" Guide (Spanish)
BROCHURE -
Rights and Benefits for Workers" Injured on the Job
BROCHURE -
Workers' Compensation Guidebook
BROCHURE - A Beginner's Guide to Workers' Compensation
Required
BROCHURE - A Guidebook for Employers in New Mexico
BROCHURE - A Guidebook for Employers in New Mexico (Spanish)
BROCHURE - An Employee's Guide to the Minnesota Workers' Compensation System
Required
BROCHURE - An Employee's Guide to the Minnesota Workers' Compensation System (Spanish)
Required
BROCHURE - An Employee's Guide to the South Dakota Workers' Compensation System
BROCHURE - An Employer's Guide to a Drug-Free Workplace
BROCHURE - Arkansas Workers' Compensation Questions & Answers
BROCHURE - Best Practices for Communication with Workers" Compensation System
BROCHURE - Best Practices for Communication with Workers" Compensation System
BROCHURE - Best Practices for Early Return to Work
BROCHURE - Best Practices for Proper Claim Reporting
BROCHURE - Best Practices for Role of the Employer
BROCHURE - Best Practices for Selecting Physicians for Your Panel
BROCHURE - Drug Free Way to Be
BROCHURE - Employee's Guide
BROCHURE - Employee's Guide (Spanish)
BROCHURE - Employer's Guide
BROCHURE - Employer's Guide to Reporting an Employee Injury
BROCHURE - Employers Frequently Asked Questions
BROCHURE - Facts about Workers' Compensation (Time of Hire Pamphlet from CA DWC)
Required
BROCHURE - Facts about Workers' Compensation(Time of Hire Pamphlet from CA DWC) (Spanish)
BROCHURE - Facts for Employers
BROCHURE - Facts for Injured Workers
BROCHURE - Facts for Injured Workers
BROCHURE - Facts for Injured Workers
BROCHURE - Facts for Injured Workers (Spanish)
BROCHURE - Highlights of the Hawaii Workers' Compensation Law
Required
BROCHURE - Important Workers' Compensation Information for Florida Employers
Required
BROCHURE - Important Workers' Compensation Information for Florida Employers (Spanish)
Required
BROCHURE - Important Workers' Compensation Information for Florida Workers
Required
BROCHURE - Important Workers' Compensation Information for Florida Workers" (Spanish)
Required
BROCHURE - Injured on the Job, an Employee's Guide to Workers' Compensation in New York State
Required
BROCHURE - Injured on the Job, an Employee's Guide to Workers' Compensation in New York State (Spanish)
Required
BROCHURE - Injured Worker's Guide to Reporting an Injury
BROCHURE - Minnesota Workers' Compensation System Employee Information Sheet
Required
BROCHURE - Minnesota Workers' Compensation System Employee Information Sheet (Spanish)
Required
BROCHURE - Notice to Employees - Tip Information
BROCHURE - Notice to Employer Regarding Obligations Under Virginia WC Act
BROCHURE - Q & A for Employees about Maryland Workers' Compensation Law
BROCHURE - Q & A for Employers about Maryland Workers' Compensation Law
BROCHURE - Questions and Answers about Workers' Compensation Law for Injured Workers - Effective July 1, 2017 - June 30, 2018
BROCHURE - Questions and Answers about Workers' Compensation Law for Injured Workers - Effective July 1, 2018 - June 30, 2019
BROCHURE - Questions and Answers about Workers' Compensation Law for Injured Workers - Effective July 1, 2019 - June 30, 2020
BROCHURE - Questions and Answers about Workers' Compensation Law for Injured Workers - Effective July 1, 2020 - June 30, 2021
BROCHURE - Questions and Answers about Workers' Compensation Law for Injured Workers Effective July 1, 2016 - June 30, 2017
BROCHURE - Questions and Answers about Workers' Compensation Law for Injured Workers" - Effective July 1, 2014 - June 30, 2015
BROCHURE - Questions and Answers about Workers' Compensation Law for Injured Workers" - Effective July 1, 2015 - June 30, 2016
BROCHURE - Rehabilitation Services for Injured Workers
BROCHURE - Rights & Obligations under the Nebraska Workers' Compensation Law
BROCHURE - Rights & Obligations under the Nebraska Workers' Compensation Law (Spanish)
BROCHURE - Stop Fraud
BROCHURE - Understanding Workers' Compensation
BROCHURE - Understanding Workers' Compensation (Spanish)
BROCHURE - Vocational Rehabilitation Services
under the Nebraska Workers'
Compensation Law (Spanish)
BROCHURE - Vocational Rehabilitation Services
under the Nebraska Workers'
Compensation Law (Spanish)
BROCHURE - Vocational Rehabilitation Services under the Nebraska Workers' Compensation Law
BROCHURE - What happens if I'm hurt on the job? (English)
Required
BROCHURE - What happens if I'm hurt on the job? (Spanish)
BROCHURE - Workbook for Injured Workers
BROCHURE - Worker's Compensation Fraud
BROCHURE - Workers" Compensation Information for Kansas Employers and Employees
BROCHURE - Workers' Compensation and You - Information for Injured Workers
BROCHURE - Workers' Compensation and You: A Guide for Injured Workers
BROCHURE - Workers' Compensation Information for the Injured Worker
BROCHURE - Workers' Compensation Information Packet
BROCHURE - Workers' Compensation Information Packet (Spanish)
BROCHURE -Brief Description of Your Rights and Benefits if You Are Injured on the Job
Required
Brochure -Handbook on Workers' Compensation and
Occupational Diseases for Injuries and Illnesses
Required
Brochure -Handbook on Workers' Compensation and
Occupational Diseases for Injuries and Illnesses (Spanish)
Required
Brochure -Handbook on Workers' Compensation and
Occupational Diseases for Injuries and Illnesses (Spanish)
Required
Brochure- Division of Workers Compensation Fact Sheet
BROCHURE-Putting Together a Safe Workplace
California SB 1159 Covid 19 Required Reporting Documentation
Required
Early Return-to-Work Initiative- Flyer
Employee Notification Letter
Employee Notification Letter (Spanish)
Employee Rights and Duties form
Required
Employer Frequently Asked Questions
EMPLOYERS: What Should I expect from my insurer?
For Employers who do not have coverage
Fraud Prevention Tips For Employers
Guide To Workers Compensation Law in South Dakota
Injured Employee Rights and Responsibilities
Injured Employee Rights and Responsibilities (Spanish)
Injured Worker Guide 2020
Injured Worker Guide 2020 - Spanish
New Employee Notice (covered and non-covered employers shall notify their employees of coverage status, in writing,
New Employee Notice -
(Spanish)
Notice - Employee Notice Ombudsman Program
Required
Notice - Employee Notice Ombudsman Program (Spanish)
Required
Notice - Employer's Notice of First Responder Liaison to Employees
Required
Notice - Employer's Notice of First Responder Liaison to Employees (Spanish)
Required
NOTICE - Important Information for Injured Employees
Required
NOTICE - Workers" Compensation Filing Information
Required
NOTICE -Information Regarding Workers' Compensation and a Claimant's Rights
NOTICE OF COMPLIANCE - Ordering information.
Notice of Compliance Information
Notice of Employer Rights and Responsibilities in a Workers’ Compensation Claim
Notice of Injured Employee Rights and Responsibilities in the Texas Workers' Compensation System
Required
Notice of Injured Employee Rights and Responsibilities in the Texas Workers' Compensation System (Spanish)
Notice of Reported Injury
Required
Notice to Employees Concerning Workers' Compensation in Texas
Required
Notice to Employees Concerning Workers' Compensation in Texas - (Spanish)
Required
Notice to Employer/Notice to Employee
Notice to Employer/Notice to Employee (Spanish)
OFFICIAL NOTICE Panel of Physicians
- (Spanish)
Required
OFFICIAL NOTICE WC/MCO Panel
Required
OFFICIAL NOTICE WC/MCO Panel - (Spanish)
Required
POSTER -
Notice of Coverage (Spanish)
Required
POSTER -
Employer Notice of Workers' Compensation Insurance Coverage- (English & Spanish)
Required
POSTER -
Employer's Compliance with Workers' Compensation Law (English and Spanish)
Required
POSTER -
Notice To Employees Poster (Spanish)
Required
POSTER - Anti-Fraud Poster
Required
POSTER - Anti-Fraud Poster (Spanish)
POSTER - Bill of Rights
Required
POSTER - Bill of Rights - (Spanish)
Required
POSTER - Broken Arm Poster
- 11 x 17 Size (Spanish)
POSTER - Broken Arm Poster - 11 x 17 Size
POSTER - Colorado Workers' Compensation Information
Required
POSTER - Colorado Workers' Compensation Information (Spanish)
Required
POSTER - Criteria to Establish an Employee or Independent Contractor
Required
POSTER - Drug Free Workplace
Required
POSTER - DWC- 7
Notice to Employees Poster - (English and Spanish)
Required
Poster - Employee Warning -Termination of Coverage
POSTER - Employees - Know Your Rights!
Required
POSTER - Employers' Notice of Insurance
Required
POSTER - Fraud Poster
Required
POSTER - Generic Notice to Employees poster.
POSTER - Health Notice for Managed Care
POSTER - Informational Poster
Required
POSTER - Job Safety and Health
Required
POSTER - Job Safety and Health Law
Required
POSTER - Labor Law
Required
POSTER - Labor Law (Spanish)
Required
POSTER - Labor Law Posters (Complete set)
Required
POSTER - N.C. Workers' Compensation Notice to Injured Workers and Employers
Required
POSTER - N.C. Workers' Compensation Notice to Injured Workers and Employers (Spanish)
Required
POSTER - Notice for Employees Poster
Required
POSTER - Notice of Coverage
Required
POSTER - Notice of Coverage
Required
POSTER - Notice Regarding Workers' Compensation
Required
POSTER - Notice Regarding Workers' Compensation - (Spanish)
Required
POSTER - Notice to Employee - Coal Miners
Required
POSTER - Notice to Employees
Required
POSTER - Notice to Employees
Required
POSTER - Notice To Employees Poster
Required
POSTER - Notice to Employer of Injury
(11 x 14)
Required
POSTER - Notice to Employer of Injury
(11 x 14)
Required
POSTER - Notice to Employer of Injury (two- 8 x 11 pages)
Required
POSTER - Noticia Sobre Compensacion Laboral
Required
POSTER - Oklahoma Workers' Compensation Notice and Instruction to Employers and Employees
Required
POSTER - Oklahoma Workers' Compensation Notice and Instruction to Employers and Employees (Spanish)
Required
POSTER - Poster of Instructions
Required
POSTER - Poster of Instructions (Spanish)
Required
POSTER - Posting Notice
Required
POSTER - Remember: It Is Important To Tell Your Employer About Your Injury
Required
POSTER - Rights and Responsibilities
POSTER - Safety on the Job Poster
Required
POSTER - Safety on the Job Poster
(Spanish)
Required
POSTER - Safety on the Job Poster
(Spanish)
Required
POSTER - Self-Insurance Poster
(English and Spanish)
Required
POSTER - Stop
Workers" Compensation Fraud Poster
Required
POSTER - Stop
Workers" Compensation Fraud Poster (Spanish)
Required
POSTER - Tennessee Workers' Compensation Insurance Posting Notice
Required
POSTER - Tennessee Workers' Compensation Insurance Posting Notice
(Spanish)
Required
POSTER - WC Act Summary
Required
POSTER - WC Act Summary Spanish)
Required
POSTER - Work Exposure to Bodily Fluids (English and Spanish)
Required
POSTER - Work Exposure to Methicillin-Resistant Staphylococcus aureus (MRSA), Spinal Meningitis, or Tuberculosis (TB)
Required
POSTER - Work Place Safety (English and Spanish)
Required
POSTER - Worker's Compensation Notice
Required
POSTER - Worker's Compensation Notice (Spanish)
Required
POSTER - Workers
POSTER - Workers'
Compensation Poster (Spanish)
Required
POSTER - Workers' Compensation
Required
POSTER - Workers' Compensation
Required
POSTER - Workers' Compensation
-
(Spanish)
Required
POSTER - Workers' Compensation -
(Spanish)
Required
POSTER - Workers' Compensation Board Notice to Employees
Required
POSTER - Workers' Compensation Notice
Required
POSTER - Workers' Compensation Notice
Required
POSTER - Workers' Compensation Notice
Required
POSTER - Workers' Compensation Notice - (Spanish)
Required
POSTER - Workers' Compensation Notice - (Spanish)
Required
POSTER - Workers' Compensation Poster
Required
POSTER - Workers' Compensation Poster
POSTER - Workers' Compensation Poster
Required
POSTER - Workers' Compensation Poster (Spanish)
Required
POSTER - Workers' Compensation Poster - (Spanish)
Required
POSTER - Workplace Notice
Required
POSTER - Workplace Notice (Spanish)
Required
POSTER - Wyoming Workers' Compensation Act
Required
POSTER - Your Rights as a Worker in Washington State
Required
POSTER -Employers Liability and Workers" Compensation Poster- (Form 31) - (Spanish)
Required
POSTER -Employers Liability and Workers" Compensation Poster (Form 31)
Required
Poster Employee Notice
Poster Employee Notice (Spanish)
Poster Employee Warning - Pending Cancellation of Coverage
Poster Regulations
Required
POSTER- WC-9 Employers Reinstatement Liability Poster
Required
Preferred Provider Program advisory notice
Preferred Provider Program Advisory Notice - (Spanish)
Preferred Provider Program notice - (Spanish)
Preferred Provider Program notice.
Report of Fraud or Abuse (Confidential)
Report of Suspected Workers
Safety and health protection on the job
Safety and health protection on the job (Spanish)
SIU Stop Fraud
Statement of Rights (WCL)
Required
Third Party Election Form / Brochure- Injured by a Third Party?
Utah Occupational Safety and Health Poster
Required
Utah Occupational Safety and Health Poster - (Spanish)
Required
WCA - POSTER - 11 x 17 version
Required
WCA - POSTER - 8-1/2 x 11 Two-part Version
Required
WCA - POSTER - Fraud Poster
Required
Workers Compensation Brochure
Workers have a right to file for workers compensation for COVID-19
Workers have a right to file for workers compensation for COVID-19-Spanish
Workers" Compensation Information form
Required
Workers" Compensation Election Information
Workers' Compensation Fraud Inspector General Complaint Form
Workers' Compensation: Fraud and Noncompliance (Brochure)
You Were Injured On The Job, What Now ?
Required
State Compliance Information
Penalties for Late Reporting
Penalties for Late Reporting
Penalties for Late Reporting
Penalties for Late Reporting
Penalties for Late Reporting
Penalties for Late Reporting
Pharmacy First Fill
Worker's Report of Injury and Release of Medical Authorization (to view and download, right mouse click on the link, select "save link as")
Medical Authorization Form
Wage Form
Travel Reimbursement - English
Travel Reimbursement - Spanish
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Injured Worker Resources
2020 Mailing Schedule for Permanent Benefit Checks
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
The mailing address for medical bills from Arizona, Colorado, New Mexico, Nevada and Utah is:
CopperPoint Insurance CompaniesMail Stop: WCS 135801PO Box 2979Clinton, IA 52733-2979
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Travel Reimbursement
Medical Provider List with Authorization
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return to Work Rule 6 TemplateReturn to Work Rule 6 for ProviderColorado - Modified Duty Process PacketColorado - Modified Duty Job OfferSupplemental Return to WorkReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
The mailing address for medical bills from Arizona, Colorado, New Mexico, Nevada and Utah is:
CopperPoint Insurance CompaniesMail Stop: WCS 135801PO Box 2979Clinton, IA 52733-2979
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Medical Records Release
Travel Reimbursement
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
The mailing address for medical bills from Arizona, Colorado, New Mexico, Nevada and Utah is:
CopperPoint Insurance CompaniesMail Stop: WCS 135801PO Box 2979Clinton, IA 52733-2979
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Travel Reimbursement
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
The mailing address for medical bills from Arizona, Colorado, New Mexico, Nevada and Utah is:
CopperPoint Insurance CompaniesMail Stop: WCS 135801PO Box 2979Clinton, IA 52733-2979
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Designated Provider List - Nevada
Pharmacy First Fill
Injured Employee's Request for Compensation (D-6)
Mileage Form D-26
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Modified Duty - NevadaReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
The mailing address for medical bills from Arizona, Colorado, New Mexico, Nevada and Utah is:
CopperPoint Insurance CompaniesMail Stop: WCS 135801PO Box 2979Clinton, IA 52733-2979
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by CopperPoint
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - English
Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) Privacy Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Medical Provider Required Information
If you are a medical provider, please complete the proper form for your state and have the injured worker sign it. The completed and signed document should be mailed within the state's reporting guidelines. Be sure to fill out the form completely.
Please include your physical address, not a post office box number.
Medical Provider Billing Information
Please direct all CopperPoint billing questions and inquiries to our medical review partner Mitchell International at 855.942.1118.
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Workers Compensation Injury Reporting Procedures Rev 06_2016
AK Employer Supervisor Notice of Occupational Injury or Illness
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill - English
Pharmacy First Fill - Spanish
Wage Statement
Authorization To Release Personal Health Information
Workers' Compensation Fraud Poster - English
Workers' Compensation Fraud Poster - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Designated Provider List - Nevada
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Majoris OR MCO Employee Enrollment Packet
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by Alaska National
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
24/7 Injury Helpline FAQ
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 1
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster English/Spanish 2
24/7 Injury Helpline Poster Spanish
24/7 Injury Helpline Overview
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
Consumer Privacy Statement
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Documents Provided by PacificComp
Portal User Guides
Pharmacy First Fill
Medical Records Release of Injured Worker
Wage Statement
Mileage Form
Fraud Poster - English
Fraud Poster - Spanish
MPN Employee Guide (Covered Employee's Notification of Rights) - English
MPN Employee Guide (Covered Employee's Notification of Rights) - Spanish
Initial Medical Referral Form
Employee Declination of Medical Treatment (EN/SP)
What You Need To Do Right Now - Policyholders Checklist
What To Do When an Injury Occurs - Policyholders Checklist
Change of Address
Witness Statement
Accident Report - English
Accident Report - Spanish
California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) Notice - English
California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) Notice - Spanish
Return To Work
Return To Work Transitional Employment Offer TemplateReturn To Work Policy Guide
Arizona | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Alabama | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Alaska | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Arkansas | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
California | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers Guide - English
California Division of Workers' Compensation (DWC) Fact Sheets
DWC Fact Sheets are documents that can be used by both the injured workers and the Policyholders to provide an overview of the laws that govern the claims administration process in the State of California. These forms are also available on the DWC website at www.dir.ca.gov
Employee Fact Sheets
All: English | SpanishFact Sheet A: Utilization Review Fact Sheet – English | SpanishFact Sheet B: Glossary of Workers’ Comp Terms – English | SpanishFact Sheet C: Temporary Disability Fact Sheet – English | SpanishFact Sheet D: Permanent Disability Fact Sheet – English | SpanishFact Sheet E: Qualified Medical Evaluation/Agreed Medical Evaluation Fact Sheet – English | Spanish
Medical Records Release of Injured Worker
When injured workers sign this form, they give PacificComp permission to obtain their medical records so that PacificComp can evaluate their claim.
English | Spanish
Mileage Reimbursement Request for Injured Worker Use
Injured workers should use this form to log their mileage for travel related to their medical treatment so that PacificComp can reimburse them.
English and Spanish
Colorado | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Resources
Connecticut | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Delaware | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Florida | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Georgia | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Hawaii | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Information
Idaho | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Illinois | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Indiana | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Iowa | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Kansas | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Kentucky | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Louisiana | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Maine | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Massachusetts | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Maryland | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Michigan | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Minnesota | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Mississippi | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Missouri | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Montana | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Nebraska | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Nevada | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Resources
New Hampshire | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
New Jersey | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
New Mexico | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s resources provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Resources
New York | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
North Carolina | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
North Dakota | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Ohio | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Oklahoma | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Oregon | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Pennslyvania | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Rhode Island | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
South Carolina | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
South Dakota | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Tennessee | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Texas | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Utah | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s resources provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Resources
Vermont | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Virginia | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Washington | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
West Virginia | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Wisconsin | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Wyoming | Injured Worker Guide
The worker’s compensation system can be complicated, and each state has its own laws regarding workers’ compensation.
The information contained in your state’s guide provides a general guide for workers injured or made ill on the job.
This state-issued publication will assist you in navigating the workers’ compensation system and serve as a resource for basic legal rights as well as steps to take to initiate workers’ compensation benefits, deadlines and who to contact for additional assistance.
If you have questions about the workers’ compensation process, this guide will provide the contact information for the regulatory agency for your state. In addition, many states have an ombudsman to oversee and assist all interested parties in the workers' compensation system.
Publications
Injured Workers' Guide
Sorry!No items currently match your filtering criteria.
Reset
